<resources>
    <string name="app_name">UTSApp_31120013_RickyYohanes</string>

    <string-array name="story_title">
        <item>The Hare and Tortoise</item>
        <item>The Dog and the Bone</item>
        <item>The Thirsty Crow</item>
        <item>Lazy John</item>
        <item>The Fox and Grapes</item>
        <item>The Ant and Grasshopper</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="story_slug">
        <item>There was once a hare who was friends with a tortoise</item>
        <item>Once there was a dog who wandered the streets night and day in search of food.</item>
        <item>A thirsty crow was wandering the forest in search of water</item>
        <item>There was a boy named John who was so lazy</item>
        <item>Once there was a hungry fox who stumbled upon a vineyard</item>
        <item>The ant and the grasshopper were good friends.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="story_description">
        <item>
            There was once a hare who was friends with a tortoise. One day, he challenged the tortoise to a race. Seeing how slow the tortoise was going, the hare thought he’ll win this easily. So he took a nap while the tortoise kept on going. When the hare woke up, he saw that the tortoise was already at the finish line. Much to his chagrin, the tortoise won the race while he was busy sleeping.
        </item>
        <item>
        Once there was a dog who wandered the streets night and day in search of food. One day, he found a big juicy bone and he immediately grabbed it between his mouth and took it home. On his way home, he crossed a river and saw another dog who also had a bone in its mouth. He wanted that bone for himself too. But as he opened his mouth, the bone he was biting fell into the river and sank. That night, he went home hungry.
        </item>
        <item>
        After flying a long distance, a thirsty crow was wandering the forest in search of water. Finally, he saw a pot half-filled with water. He tried to drink from it but his beak wasn’t long enough to reach the water inside. He then saw pebbles on the ground and one by one, he put them in the pot until the water rose to the brim. The crow then hastily drank from it and quenched his thirst.
        </item>
        <item>
        There was a boy named John who was so lazy, he couldn’t even bother to change his clothes. One day, he saw that the apple tree in their yard was full of fruits. He wanted to eat some apples but he was too lazy to climb the tree and take the fruits. So he lay down underneath the tree and waited for the fruits to fall off. John waited and waited until he was very hungry but the apples never fell.
        </item>
        <item>
        Once there was a hungry fox who stumbled upon a vineyard. After seeing the round, juicy grapes hanging in a bunch, the fox drooled. But no matter how high he jumped, he couldn’t reach for it. So he told himself that it was probably sour and left. That night, he had to sleep on an empty stomach.
        </item>
        <item>
        The ant and the grasshopper were good friends. In the summer, the ant works hard to fill his storage with food. While the grasshopper was enjoying the fine weather and playing all day. When winter came, the ant was lying cozily in his home surrounded by the food he stored during the summer. While the grasshopper was in his home, hungry and freezing. He asked the ant for food and the ant gave him some. But it wasn’t enough to last the entire winter. When he tried to ask the ant again, the latter replied: “I’m sorry my friend but my food is just enough for my family to last until the end of winter. If I give you more, we too will starve. We had the entire summer to prepare for the winter but you chose to play instead.”
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="story_moral">
        <item>
            The hare teaches that overconfidence can sometimes ruin you. While the tortoise teaches us about the power of perseverance.
        </item>
        <item>
            If we always envy what others have, we’ll end up losing what we already have, just like the greedy dog.
        </item>
        <item>
            If there’s a will, there’s a way. Every problem has a solution if we just look hard enough and don’t give up.
        </item>
        <item>
            Laziness can get you nowhere. If you want something, you need to work hard for it.
        </item>
        <item>
            When we want something but think it’s too hard to attain, we make up excuses. We tell ourselves that it’s probably not that great instead of working hard for it.
        </item>
        <item>
            Winter, in this story, represents a time in our life where food and resources are scarce. While summer is that time where everything is abundant. So if you have a lot right now, save some of it for the winter.
        </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>